Miss World 1970: The launch of a revolution
Misbehaviour is a drama, history, comedy film directed by Philippa Lowthorpe.
A group of women involved in the Women's Liberation Movement hatched a plan to invade the stage and disrupt the live broadcast
at the 1970 Miss World competition in London, resulting in overnight fame for the newly-formed organization.
When the show resumed, the results caused an uproar and
turned the Western ideal of beauty on its head.
Sally Alexander, played by Keira Knightley.
Jennifer Hosten - Miss Grenada, played by Gugu Mbatha-Raw.
Jo Robinson, played by Jessie Buckley.
Julia Morley, played by Keeley Hawes.
Evelyn Alexander, played by Phyllis Logan.
Dolores Hope, played by Lesley Manville.
Misbehaviour is a 2020 British comedy-drama film directed by Philippa Lowthorpe, from a
screenplay by Gaby Chiappe and Rebecca Frayn, from a story by Frayn.
The film stars Keira Knightley, Gugu Mbatha-Raw, Jessie Buckley, Keeley Hawes,
Phyllis Logan, Lesley Manville, Rhys Ifans and Greg Kinnear.
Misbehaviour was released in the United Kingdom on 13 March 2020 by Pathé's distribution
partner Walt Disney Studios Motion Pictures through 20th Century Fox.
It is the final film from Pathé UK to be released
under the 20th Century Fox name.
The film explores themes of london, england, 1970s,
commune, affectation, beauty contest.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.